Come, O Source of endless mercy,
Loose my tongue to sing Thy grace.
Streams of goodness, ever flowing,
Fill the hollows in this soul of mine.
I have tasted bitter waters,
Trying to satisfy the thirst.
But the Shepherd’s voice spoke clearly—
Called this wandering stranger home.
Come to Me, all worn and weary.
Look to Me, and live.
Learn of Me — My grace sustains you.
Can you hear Me… calling your name?
Now I speak in words of plainness:
With Thy help this far I’ve come.
I hope by Thy tender mercy
Safely to return back home.
Far from Thee and full of questions,
I knelt down and poured out my soul.
He healed every empty place in me,
Made my broken vessel whole.
My arms are open.
My wounded heart still beats for you.
My hands will bless you.
The marks of your worth remain on Me.
By Thy goodness, I was found.
Now I bear a joyful debt to carry!
To Thy grace I am now bound.
Turn now my wandering heart to Thee:
Prone to wander, Lord, I feel it,
Prone to leave the path You’ve shown;
Here’s my soul — O take and seal it,
Bring me to my heavenly home.
Take My name upon you.
The marks of your worth remain on Me.
You are no stranger now—
I call you by name.
Bring my heavenly home to me,
And bring me to my heavenly home.